let questions = [{
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the rarest M&M colour ?",
        answer: "brown",
        options: [
            "red",
            "green",
            "brown",
            "yellow"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Who are the stepsisters of Cinderella ?",
        answer: "Anastasia and Drizella",
        options: [
            "Mary and Snow White",
            "Anastasia and Mirabella",
            "Mary and Tiana",
            "Anastasia and Drizella"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Whoever threw that paper you mom's a ....",
        answer: "h*e",
        options: [
            "h*e",
            "fish",
            "dog",
            "block"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Who won the most Ballon d'Or awards?",
        answer: "Lionel Messi",
        options: [
            "Jamal",
            "Lionel Messi",
            "Cristiano Ronaldo",
            "Karim Benzema"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What height is the tallest man in the world ?",
        answer: "2.51 m",
        options: [
            "1.98 m",
            "2.30 m",
            "2.51 m",
            "1.50 m"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What is the longest marathon in the world ? ",
        answer: "5000 km",
        options: [
            "6700 km",
            "3900 km",
            "2800 km",
            "5000 km"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the most popular ecuation in the world ?",
        answer: "E=mc²",
        options: [
            "E=mc²",
            "a²=b²+c²",
            "F=m*a",
            "i²=-1"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What was bitcoin's highest price ?",
        answer: "64.800",
        options: [
            "40.000",
            "67.000",
            "100.000",
            "64.800"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is the most popular longery car brand ?",
        answer: "Mercedes Benz",
        options: [
            "Tesla",
            "BMW",
            "Porsche",
            "Mercedes Benz"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "What did Thomas Edison invent ?",
        answer: "all of them",
        options: [
            "Incandescent light bulb",
            "Gramophone",
            "all of them",
            "Phonograph cylinder"
        ]
    },
